A Guide to the Records of George Bernard Lorraine, ca. 1925-1976
Library of Virginia
- Real estate records (Box 1-149)
  - Virginia real estate (Box 1-146)
    - Mathews County (Box 79-94)
      - Mathews Land Company: 1964 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Mead, Harry Judson: 30 acres, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Maskins, J.W.: 3 acres, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Michael, Mrs.: 10 acres, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Miller, George: 5 acres, 1956-1958 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - Miller, H.L.: 46 acres, 1937 (Box 90, Folder 21)
      - Miller, J.W.: 10 acres, 1951-1953 (Box 90, Folder 22)
      - Miles, T.E.: 1937 (Box 90, Folder 23)
      - Mitchem, W.G.: 48 acres, 1948-1954 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Morris, John T.: 6 acres, 1947-1949 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Nelson, Mr.: 5 acres, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Noonan, Mr.: 6 acres, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Nottingham, Mrs.: 29 acres, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Orrell, Captain: 34 acres, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Otey, C.E.: 140 acres, 1942-1947 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Ott, Mrs.: 15 acres, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Palmer, Giles: 10 acres, 1946 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Patterson, William H.: 10 acres, 1956-1963 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Payne, S.E.: 12 1/2 acres, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Phone, B.: 40 acres, 1950-1953 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Pierce, Mrs.: 17 acres, 1955-1958 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Plunkett, G.R.: 1948 (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Plunkett, G.R.: 47 acres, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Postles, F.J.: 28 acres, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Pugh, Frank: 3 acres, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 17)
      - Purkins, Mr.: 8 acres, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - Rhea, Mr.: 1950 (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - Richardson, Mr.: 30 acres, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - Richardson, Mr.: 1957 (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - Rilee, R.M.: 143 acres, 1944-1950 (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - Rishel, Mr.: 7 acres, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 23)
      - Rishel, Mr.: 1967 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Rishel, John: 1/4 acres, 1957-1958 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Rousek, Charles: 1955 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Rowe, B.T.: 1958 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Rubaiz, Mrs.: 2 acres, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Ryer, Henry S.: 10 acres, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Sanders, Mr.: 11 acres, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Sanders, J.W.: 20 acres, 1955 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Scheer, Dr.: 10 acres, 1950 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Schmarze, T.A.: 4 1/2 acres, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Schmidt, Mr.: 1955 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Shepherd, J.E.: 1945 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Shepherd, John E.: 30 acres, 1937-1945 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Shipp, Cal: 30 acres, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Shirey, Francis M.: 27 1/2 acres, 1949-1950 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Sadler, Blanche: 7 acres, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Sadler, C.F.: 3 acres, 1946 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Simpson, Mr.: 1 acre, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Smith, A.M.: 7 acres, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Smith, George F.: 12 acres, 1939-1941 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Smith, William E.: 1 3/4 acres, 1952-1954 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Smithers, Charles R.: 30 acres, 1936 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Stevenson, O.M.: 1957 (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Stoakes, Estelle: 96 acres, 1936 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Stutzman, Dr.: 3 acres, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Tate, A.E.: 10 acres, 1947-1953 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Tatterson, W.B.: 2 acres, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Thomas, Mrs.: 3 acres, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Thompson, Mr.: 20 acres, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - Thurston, Mr.: 17 acres, 1949 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Tupper, Mrs.: 1959 (Box 93, Folder 18)
      - Twine, R.B.: 25 acres, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - Tyler, Bright H.: 1955-1957 (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - Van de Wiele, D.L.: 33 acres, 1946 (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Walker, Captain: 4 acres, 1947 (Box 93, Folder 22)
      - Walker, F.A.: 2 acres, 1950-1953 (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - Ward, Mr.: 3 acres, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 24)
      - Warren, W. Preston: 72 acres, 1947-1955 (Box 93, Folder 25)
      - Washington, Mary T.: 160 1/2 acres, 1936-1937 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - White, Bernard F.: 10 acres, 1945-1946 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - White, E. Lee: 7 1/2 acres, 1946 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - White, L.D.: 15 acres, 1947-1949 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Williams, Miss: 1955 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Willis, Colonel: 3 acres, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Willis, Edward F.: 60 acres, 1947 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Wolff, Mrs.: 1/4 acres, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Wolff, Mrs.: 3 acres, 1952 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Wright, Maude L.: 36 acres, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified property: 129 acres, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1935 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1937-1957, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 94, Folder 14-16)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box 95)
      - Boswell Avenue subdivision: 1946 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Kinderton: 350 acres, 1941 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Merry Mount: H.O. Swink, 1942 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Palmer Springs: 1 3/4 acres, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Prestwould: William T. Hughes, 1945 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Prudin, James Richard: 1951 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Wilson, Homer: 1955 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933, 1937 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Middlesex County (Box 96-103)
      - Ashland: Robert Watson Eubank, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Barn Elms: C.D. Marchant, 1936 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Bay View: J.H. Norris, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Beechwood: P.F. Chewning, 1945-1958 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Berryville Farm: F.W. Scott, 1947 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Berryville Farm: Mr. Curry, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Canoe Farm: Julian Tyler, 1939 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Corbin Hall: John E. Jackson, 1931-1940 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Corbin Hall: L.R. Miller, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Deer Chase: M.A. Pratt, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Fairfield Farm: S.L. Sinnott, 1938-1940 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Fairfield Farm: Eastman O'Riordan, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Gray Point: J.I. Adams, 1944-1945 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Hilliard's Mill Pond: Fannie Richardson, 1948-1949 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - House Point: H.E. Baumberger, 1944-1948 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Kilmer Point: Harold Barnes, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Lansdowne: John F. Upton, 1936-1961 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Laurel Bank: A.J. Chewning, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Locust Grove: James Keith, 1932-1943 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Martieu: H. Laurie Smith, 1947-1952 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Max R.: 30 acres, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Millmont: E.E. Franck, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Millstone: A.C. Powell, 1937 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - North End Plantation: John G. McGurk, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Nesting: Margaret Gordon, 1936-1942 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Old Gayle Place: F.E. Williams, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Old Norris Home: S.J. Moore, 1947 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Pines: Henry M. Ufford, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Powell Place: Bank of Middlesex, 1937 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Providence: Addie Wake, 1959 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Remlick Hall: Alexander M. Robb, 1940-1943 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Remlick Hall: photographs (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Remlick Hall: V.H. Gill, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Rosegill: Benjamin Temple, 1935-1940 (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - Rosegill: photographs (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - Rosegill: R.F.B. Steele, 1944 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Rosegill: photographs (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Rosegill: photographs (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Rosegill: Virginia Landmark Corporation, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Roseneath Farm: B.S. Morgan, 1949-1953 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Shooter's Hill: W.C. Moody, 1936 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Shooter's Hill: Harold Barnes, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Urbanna Beach Hotel: Alfred L. Blake, 1949-1953 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Waverly: John W. Morgan, 1946-1952 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - White Gate Farm: Walter G. Cocks, 1947-1956 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - White Point Guest House: W. Matt Moltz, 1947 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Wilton Plantation: Gerald L. Ballantine, 1933-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Woodport: Herbert C. Blake, 1945 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Woodport: W.T. Wright, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Barnes, Mr.: 400 acres, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Barnes, H.G.: 1950-1954 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Bishop, L.W.: 1969 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Bowles, Mrs.: 1944-1949 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Bristow, Marshall A.: 137 acres, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Brooks, C.L.: 1958 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Callis, W.R.: 1949 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Clark, Y.D.: 1951 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Crittendon, John F.: 98 acres, 1944 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Crittendon, John F.: 97 acres, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - Crittendon, Lucille: 125 acres, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      - Daniel, S.W.: 112 acres, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 15)
      - Easton, William B.: 25 acres, 1944-1953 (Box 99, Folder 16)
      - Gatzek, Warner J.: 5 acres, 1964-1967 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      - Gerding, Leroy E.: 5 acres, 1955-1960 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Gillis, Joe: 63 acres, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Gwathmey, William R.: 12 acres, 1947-1949 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Harper, F.W.: 2 acres, 1933 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Harwood, J.W.: 1941 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Hawksworth, Tom T.: 1944-1947 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Holding, Samuel H.: 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Holmes, J.C.: 1962 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Hummel, Fred: 1948-1958 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Hunter, E.M.: 1948 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - King, Mr.: 22 acres, 1945 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - King, J.S.: 5 3/4 acres, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Kohn, Theodore: 1948 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - Layport, John E.: 1965 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Long, L.W.: 8 1/2 acres, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - MacDonald, R.F.: 2 acres, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - McKinlay, J.M.: 1959 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Major, A.O.: 1949 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - Marston, Mr.: 1941-1945 (Box 100, Folder 19)
      - Maryland-Virginia Farm Agency: 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 20)
      - Masters, Howard R.: 5 acres, 1952-1960 (Box 100, Folder 21)
      - Matthews, R.H.: 39 acres, 1944 (Box 100, Folder 22)
      - Mayes, M.S.: 33 acres, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 23)
      - Miller, William C.: 4 1/2 acres, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 24)
      - Moller, Robert: 1963 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Moody, William G.: 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Moore, S.J.: 1948-1949 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Neal, Dr.: 1947 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Norton, C.B.: 9 3/4 acres, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Page, W.A.: 1947 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Parker, Mr.: 10 acres, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Parker, Kibler: 1947 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Parker, P.A.: 17 acres, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Patterson, Wilson E.: 18 acres, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - Rewa, Edward: 1946 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Rewa, Edward: 1961 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Saunders, E.B.: 23 acres, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - Stiff, C. Nelson: 24 acres, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Stiff, John C.: 8 acres, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Stiff, J.W.: 5 3/4 acres, 1945 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Taylor, Preston F.: 10 acres, 1943-1944 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Terrell, Hazel: 1958 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Tinsley, Mary H.: 203 1/2 acres, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Towell, R.B.: 23 acres, 1947 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Towell, R.B.: 1945-1948 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Towell, R.B.: 3 acres, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Trapnil, Mr.: 22 acres, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Trennant, Louise: n.d. (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Wake, B.D.: 43 acres, 1944-1947 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - Walker, Bradford: 5 acres, 1949 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - Wallace, Sue: 90 acres, 1944 (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - Webb, Blanche S.: 1954 (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - Wilkins, George Y.: 17 acres, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - Woodard, James A.: 1951 (Box 102, Folder 16)
      - Unidentified cottage on Hello Bay: photographs (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1957 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Montgomery County (Box 103, Folder 4-6)
      - Walnut Grove Farm: W.T. Doosing, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Willow View Farm: Waldo H. Prince, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Nansemond County (Box 104, Folder 1-4)
      - Cedar Crest Hill: James E. Culbreth, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Cherry Grove: Nellie Pittman, 1944 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Mulberry Grove: Fonita H. Bedgood, 1941 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1935-1938 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Nelson County (Box 104-105)
      - Blue Ridge Terrace Inn: F.H. Schroeder, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Cove Creek House: John Adams Christoffel, 1963-1964 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Elk Mountain: 1937 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Faber: Mr. Clark, 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Forest Edge: Mr. Burruss, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Forkfield: J.L. Gray, 1942 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Highland Lodge: Susan P.W. Burks, 1934-1936 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Inglewood: R.T. Carleton, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Locust Lawn: K.C. Mawyer, 1936 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Midway: Mary Grace Simpson, 1942 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Nelmont: Phillip T. Harris, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Oak Hill: S.M. Page, 1938 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Oak Ridge: 1935 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Oakland Farm: Frances L. Towers, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - Red Apple Orchard: George B. Clifford & Company, 1946 (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - River Circle Farm: F. Schilling, 1942 (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Union Hill: Lucy G. Cabell, 1942 (Box 104, Folder 21)
      - Valley Farm: John R. Dixon, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Woodley Estate: 247 acres, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Gilliam, Eugene: 2 acres, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Ives, Margaret S.: 1955 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Ward, W.C.: 10 acres, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1927, 1938-1939 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - New Kent County (Box 105-106)
      - Brick House Farm: W.L. Jeffries, 1936-1939 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Camp Orapax: YMCA, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Cedar Grove: Frank Piles, 1936 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Cedar Grove: William Phipps, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Christ's Cross: P.S. Pomfrey, 1934-1959 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Cousaic Farm: Mr. Nichols, 1937 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Cumberland Farm: Benjamin H. Brenton, 1941-1947 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Cumberland Farm: photographs (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Cumberland Farm: Coleman Hunter, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Cumberland Farm: Coleman Hunter, 1973-1975 (Box 105, Folder 17)
      - Cumberland Shooting Preserve: 1975 (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Dogwood Dell: Earl R. Hamilton, 4 acres, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 19)
      - Forbes Hunting Preserve: William P. Forbes, 1936-1937 (Box 105, Folder 20)
      - Laurel Hill: W.W. Richardson, 1949-1959 (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Long Quarter: A.D. McKay, 1941 (Box 105, Folder 22)
      - McKay Farm: D.D. Burton, 1947 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Mountcastle: Carroll D. Hagan, 1934-1939 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - North Green: R.W. Taylor, 1934-1939 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Northberry: C.E. Robinson, 1936-1954 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Orapax: W.S. Potts, 1936-1940 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Orapax: Mr. Hicks, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Poplar Grove: Frank V. Baldwin, 1934-1941 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Rose Cottage: L.T. Southall, 1954 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - South Garden: Fred Pfano, 1936-1939 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Wahrani: W.B. Keys, 1953 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Waterloo Farm: Henry S. James, 1936-1938 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Woodburn: Mr. Sriggs, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Farthing, W.G.: 16 acres, 1955 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Perry, V.B.: 440 acres, 1945 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Smith, L.M.: 3 acres, 1948 (Box 106, Folder 15)
      - Walker, H.B.: 800 acres, 1940 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      - Unidentified island property: n.d. (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1932-1940, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Norfolk City and County (Box 107, Folder 1-4)
      - Hempstead: Frederick R. Barrett, 1947 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Mackay, R.C.: 1948 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1940 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Northampton County (Box 107, Folder 5-15)
      - Vaucluse: Roy Wheeler (realtor), n.d. (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Daniel, John T.: 1934 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Holland, G.W.: 1934 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Mears, F.W.: 100 acres, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Scott, Marion: 100 acres, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Spady, Garnett: 1934 (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Travis, Charles F.: 200 acres, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Webster, G.L.: 1934 (Box 107, Folder 12)
      - Wilkins, George F.: 114 acres, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 13)
      - Wilkins, W.W.: 1934 (Box 107, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Northumberland County (Box 108-119)
      - Bell Cove: Donald Jones, 1949 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - By-the-Sea: Edward G. Evans, 1943 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Cherry Hill: Potomac Supply Company, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Cloverdale: Dr. Coates, 1947-1949 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Cobbs Hall: W.H. Harvey, 1937 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Coppedge Farm: James A. Haydon, 1943-1947 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Cypress Farm: Kramer Thomas, 1941 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Farnefold: 1969 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Fauntleroy: Housing Investments Corporation, 1933-1944 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Forest Lodge: R.H. Horner, 1947-1956 (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Gascony: Annie H. Spicer, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Gascony: William A. Rudasill, 1953 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Goodman property: 1957 (Box 108, Folder 13)
      - Hard Scrabble: John T. Litchfield, 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 14)
      - Hillcrest Farm: Edwin J. Dietz, 1949-1951 (Box 108, Folder 15)
      - Holly Ridge: W. Stanley Bull, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 16)
      - Hollycroft: G.P. Newton, 1958 (Box 108, Folder 17)
      - Indian Creek Condominiums: J. Norris Blake & Associates, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 18)
      - Ingleside: Mr. Tignor, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 19)
      - Locksley Hall: Locksley Hall Corporation, 1957 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Locksley Hall: Locksley Hall Corporation, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Locksley Hall: John Frese, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Locksley Hall: Aubrey Lee, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Locksley Hall: n.d. (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Locksley Hall: Locksley Hall Corporation, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Locksley Hall: Julio Brancoli, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - Locksley Hall: A.R. Seig, 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - Locksley Hall: R.M. Langdon, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Locksley Hall: Locksley Hall Corporation, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Locksley Hall: Mr. Parrish, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 11)
      - Locksley Hall: Mr. Hare, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Locksley Hall: Locksley Hall Corporation, 1966-1967 (Box 109, Folder 13)
      - Locksley Hall: Basil Spalding, 1965-1970 (Box 109, Folder 14)
      - Locust Grove: E.S. Headley, 1937 (Box 109, Folder 15)
      - Locust Grove: Walter Clark, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 16)
      - Magnolia: Edward P. Tignor, 1939-1946 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Mantua: Wayne Chatfield-Taylor, 1942 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Mantua: James W. Mullin, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Mount Zion: Herbert Darion Borker, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Natty Point Farm: L.V. Johnson, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Northumberland Motel: Edwin J. Deitz, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Old Mohundro: Walter L. Gruner, 1963-1966 (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - Orchard Cove: G.T. Travers, 1955 (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Red Gate: Joseph LeGrand, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - Salt Pond: S.A. Whitaker, 1936-1950 (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - Snowden: A.C. Gibson, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 11)
      - Springfield: Joseph LeGrand, 1942-1961 (Box 110, Folder 12)
      - Springfield: photographs (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - Springfield: photographs (Box 110, Folder 14)
      - Springfield: photographs (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Springfield: advertising plaques (Box 110, Folder 16-17)
      - Story Book House: Admiral Jackson, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Sunnybank: Rice-Packer Real Estate Agency, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Sunnyside: J. Gordon Michaels, 1968-1971 (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Texas Farm: Edward L. Traylor, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Tidewater Imp. Company: Richard Hayden, 1956 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Tranquility: John C. Little, 1961 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Tucker Point: Virgil Randolph, 1945-1960 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Walnut Point: James Lewis, 1961 (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - West End Farm: Richard T. Ellis, 1937-1943 (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - West End: Henry G. Thorndike, 1951-1964 (Box 111, Folder 10)
      - West End: n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Wheatland: J.B. Jeffress, 1935-1943 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Wheatland: Charles Cardwell, 1946-1963 (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - Wheatland: W.L. Palmer, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Wheatland: Adolph Prochazka, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Wicomico View: Edna S. Hudnall, 1945-1946 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Yeacomic View: 324 acres, 1963 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Adams, J.I.: 212 acres, 1942 (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - Allen, Covington K.: 10 acres, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Ashburn, L.R.: n.d. (Box 112, Folder 10)
      - Boone, Lee C.: 2 acres, 1947-1949 (Box 112, Folder 11)
      - Bowles, Roland: 26 acres, 1956-1957 (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - Bradner, J.R.: 1956 (Box 112, Folder 13)
      - Braun, Mr.: 6 acres, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 14)
      - Brooks, C.E.: 52 1/2 acres, 1957 (Box 112, Folder 15)
      - Byrnes, Colonel: 2 acres, 1956 (Box 112, Folder 16)
      - Choate, C.C.: 2 acres, 1955 (Box 112, Folder 17)
      - Cockrell, Dr.: 1961 (Box 112, Folder 18)
      - Cockrell, Stanley: 10 acres, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 19)
      - Colby, William E.: 1 acre, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 20)
      - Coppedge, Thomas R.: n.d. (Box 112, Folder 21)
      - Craig, Mrs.: 62 acres, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - Cranshaw, Mr.: 8 acres, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Dameron, Mrs.: 37 acres, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - Dameron, Edward Page: 50 acres, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - Davis, A.K.: 11 acres, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - Davis, D.V.: 5 1/2 acres, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - DeBurr, S.L.: 245 acres, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 7)
      - Deitz, Helen P.: 1952 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - Deveraux, Frederick: n.d. (Box 113, Folder 9)
      - Dickinson, George F.: 30 acres, 1948-1956 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - Duncan, S.T.: 16 acres, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 11)
      - Edmunds, D.A.: 1963 (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - Edmunds, D.A.: 2 1/2 acres, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - Edwards, Captain: 3 acres, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 14)
      - Edwards, Betty: 3 acres, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 15)